Finding Aid for Sam Sturgis Photograph collection
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Ypsilanti
  - Manchester Hardware store, Y 152 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
AA 2.30, AA 2.31, AA 2.32, AA 2.36, AA 2.37, AA 2.38, AA 2.40, AA 2.41, AA 2.42, AA 2.45, AA 5, AA 6, AA 17, AA 18, AA 21, AA 26B, AA 26C, AA 26D, AA 27C, AA 27D, AA 27E
AA 32B, AA 32F, AA 34A, AA 34D, AA 35A, AA 35B, AA 35C, AA 43, AA 52, AA 60, AA 67, AA 79, AA 80, AA 88, AA 91, AA 90, AA 89, AA 92, AA 94
AA 105A, AA 135, AA 136, AA 137, AA 139, AA 139, AA 140, AA 156, AA 158
AA 219, AA 220, AA 221.3, AA 221.7, AA 221.11, AA 221.15, AA 221.36, AA 224, AA 227, AA 228.11
AA 232.3, AA 232.4, AA 232.5, AA 232.6, AA 232.8, AA 232.9, AA 238, AA 243, AA 244.11, AA 244.14, AA 244.22, AA 244.24, AA 245, AA 246, AA 255.7, AA 255.10, AA 258.1
AA 260, AA 263, AA 264A, AA 264B, AA 264C, AA 264D, AA 266.1, AA 266.2, AA 272.4, AA 273.8, AA 273.35, AA 273.36, AA 273.42, AA 273.50, AA 273.53, AA 273.54, AA 274.2
AA 276, AA 277.1, AA 277.2, AA 278.1, AA 278.2, AA 286, AA 290
AA 301, AA 302, AA 303, AA 305, AA 306, AA 307, AA 309, AA 310, AA 315,AA 326, AA 327, AA 328, AA 331, AA 348, AA 349
AA 350, AA 353, AA 353A, AA 356, AA 360, AA 380, AA 384, AA 385, AA 399
AA 404, AA 413, AA 414, AA 417, AA 419, AA 420, AA 421, AA 422, AA 424, AA 425, AA 426, AA 432, AA 433, AA 434, AA 437, AA 438, AA 441
AA 462, AA 468, AA 469, AA 470, AA 475, AA 484, AA 486, AA 495
AA 513, AA 517, AA 518, AA 519.1, AA 519.3, AA 521, AA 529, AA 530, AA 531, AA 532, AA 533, AA 534, AA 535, AA 536, AA 537, AA 538, AA 539, AA 539, AA 540, AA 541, AA 542, AA 552, AA 553A, AA 554
AA 558, AA 570, AA 571, AA 575, AA 573, AA 576-578, AA 586
AA 606, AA 638, AA 639, AA 640, AA 641, AA 642, AA 648, AA 652, AA 660, AA 661, AA 664, AA 674, AA 683, AA 684, AA 685, AA 689, AA 711, AA 718
Families - Brighton
B 3, B 14, B 23, B 39, B 41, B 44, B 46, B 49, B 50, B 53, B 54, B 55, B 57, B 58, B 59, B 62, B 63, B 65, B 66, B 69, B 70, B 76, B 79, B 83, B 85, B 86, B 87, B 90, B 99, B 100, B 101, B 102, B 103, B 104, B 105, B 109, B 112, B 113, B 114
Families, Chelsea
C 1.1, C 1.8, C 1.9, C 1.14, C 1.17, C 1.20, C 1.21, C 1.22, C 1.26, C 1.27, C 1.28, C 1.31, C 2.1, C 2.6, C 2.8, C 2.9, C 2.10, C 2.11, C 2.13, C 2.14, C 2.16, C 2.18, C 3.8, C 3.9, C 3.14, C 4.3, C 6.2, C 8.1, C 8.2, C 9.2, C 9.4, C 10.1, C 10.2, C 12, C 13.2, C 13.3, C 13.5, C 13.6, C 13.7, C 15.1, C 15.4, C 15.5, C 17.2, C 19, C 22.2, C 22.4, C 22.5, C 22.7, C 25.3, C 25.8, C 25.10, C 26, C 27, C 28.1
Families, Chelsea-Manchester
CM 2.2, CM 2.4, CM 11, CM 12.3, CM 15, CM 24, CM 28, CM 28, CM 29, CM 31, CM 32, CM 36, CM 36, CM 42, CM 46, CM 48, CM 54, CM 55, CM 56, CM 57, CM 58
CM 60, CM 59, CM 61, CM 62, CM 63, CM 64, CM 65, CM 66, CM 67, CM 67, CM 68, CM 69, CM 70, CM 71, CM 72, CM 73, CM 74, CM 75, CM 76, CM 77, CM 78, CM 79
CM 80, CM 82, CM 83, CM 84, CM 85, CM 86, CM 87, CM 88, CM 89, CM 90, CM 85
Families - Dexter
DE 5, DE 7, DE 8, DE 12, DE 13, DE 16, DE 17, DE 28, DE 30, DE 33, DE 34, DE 36, DE 37, DE 38, DE 39, DE 40, DE 45
DE 51, DE 53, DE 55, DE 56, DE 58, DE 61, DE 62, DE 63, DE 66, DE 71, DE 72, DE 76, DE 77, DE 78, DE 79
DE 81, DE 85, DE 87, DE 90, DE 101, DE 104, DE 109, DE 112
Families, Dixboro
DI 3, DI 14, DI 24, DI 26, DI 28, DI 29, DI 30, DI 31, DI 34, DI 35, DI 36, DI 39, DI 40
Families, Manchester
M 1, M 4, M 9, M 10, M 13, M 17, M 34, M 35, M 35, M 39, M 42, M 51, M 52, M 54, M 56, M 63, M 65, M 66, M 76
M 80, M 82, M 83, M 84, M 85, M 86, M 87, M 88, M 89, M 91, M 93, M 95, M 97, M 98, M 99
M 101, M 102, M 103, M 106, M 109, M 112, M 114, M 116, M 117, M 118, M 119, M 120, M 121, M 123
Families, Saline
S 7, S 2, S 5, S 13, S 14, S 20, S 21, S 22, S 23, S 25, S 29, S 34, S 35, S 40, S 45, S 48, S 50, S 51, S 56
Families, Ypsilanti
Y 6, Y 24, Y 25, Y 26, Y 29, Y 37, Y 49, Y 51, Y 53, Y 54, Y 55, Y 56, Y 57, Y 58, Y 77, Y 78, Y 79, Y 82, Y 88, Y 94, Y 102, Y 104, Y 115, Y 116, Y 117, Y 118, Y 124, Y 125, Y 131, Y 142
Farm Light and Power Company
CM 2.1, CM 2.2
Farmer and Mechanics Bank
AA 232.10B, AA 232.10C, AA, 232.10D
Farmer's Market
AA 17, AA 18, AA 503.5, AA 619, AA, 620, AA 720
Farmers and Mechanics Bank
AA 7, AA 8, AA 9, AA 98, AA, 99, AA 100, AA 101, AA 232.10A
Farms and Farming
AA 276, AA 715, B 93, B 101, CM 2.3, CM 2.3, CM 36, CM 36, CM 82, CM 50
DE 28, DE 38, DE 43, DE 45, DE 95, DE 96, DE 97, DE, 98
DI 19, DI 40, M 82, M 119, M 120, S 36, S 37, S 38, S 40, S 41, S 42, S 43
Fashion
C 25.9, CM 6
Fausel
M 76, M 93
Fausel Jewelry Store
M 76, M 93
Fawcett House
AA 358
Federal Building
AA 221.36, AA 473
Federal Screw Works
CM 51, CM 52
Feiner Glass
AA 521
Fenn
CM, 69, CM 48
Fenn & Vogel Drug Store
CM 48
Fenn & Vogel Drugs
C 1.22
Ferdon Street
AA 273.25
Ferry Field
AA 260, AA 273.33, AA 277.1, AA 277.2, AA, 700, AA 704
Fiegel
AA 35C, AA 266.2
Fiegel's Menswear
AA 266.2
Fifth Avenue
AA 19, AA 61, AA 126, AA 132, AA 221.36, AA 222, AA 241.3, AA 244.10, AA 253, AA 258.6, AA 270.3, AA 271.3, AA 282.1, AA 473, AA 709, AA 223
Fifth Street
AA 20, B 30, B 140, DE 84, DE 91
Fifth Ward
AA 28B, AA 485
Fifth Ward School
AA 482, AA 483
Fillmore
DE 87
Filmore
DE 13
Finnell
AA 718
Fire Engines
AA 162, Y 35
Fires
AA 12, AA 25, AA 27A, AA 37, AA 71, AA 92, AA 127, AA 131, AA 188, AA 221.4, AA 221.22, AA 221.23, AA 221.24, AA 221.30, AA 229A, AA 229B, AA 229C, AA 236.1, AA 244.10, AA 244.27
AA 253, AA 257.1, AA 257.2, AA 257.3, AA 257.4, AA 257.5, AA 258.1, AA 258.2, AA 258.3, AA 258.4, AA 258.5, AA 263, AA 264A, AA 264B, AA 264C, AA 264D
AA 270.1, AA 270.2, AA 270.3, AA 272.9, AA 273.14, AA 281.3, AA 373, AA 380, AA 381, AA 387, AA 403, AA 407, AA 512, AA 584
B 64, C 1.21, C 1.28, C 8.2, C 8.3, C 16.4, CM 13.1, CM 13.2, CM 14, DE 23, DE 30, M 8, Y 8, Y 35, Y 72, Y 74
First Bethlehem United Church
AA 6
First Defiance Brigade
AA 258.7
First Elementary School
C 2.4
First Lutheran Church
AA 266A
First Methodist Church
C 4.1
First Michigan Infantry
M 71
First National Bank
AA 521, AA 659, AA 690, AA 691, 692, AA 693
First Regiment
Y 93
First St., Mary's Catholic School
C 16.3, C 16.4
First Street
AA 6, AA 29H, AA 208, AA 209, AA 210, 298, AA 305, AA 567, AA 639
First Tailor Shop
AA 638
First United Methodist Church
B 36
First Ward
AA 28D
Fischer
AA 241.3, AA 529, AA 718
Fischer and Finnell Store
AA 289, AA 718
Fischer's Hardware
AA 241.3, AA 529
Fishing
AA 515.5
Fitch Street
B 11, B 50, B 78
Flanders Manufacturing Company
C 1.19, C 1.30
Fleming Creek
AA 282.6, AA 282.7
Fleming Creek Bridge
AA 282.7
Fleming Creek Dam
AA 282.6
Fletcher
Y 51
Flood
AA 624, AA 625
Flour Mill Machinery
Y 132
Foland
B 83
Foley
C, 28.1
Follett House
Y 38
Football
AA 105, AA 105A, AA 227, AA 333, AA 333A, 333B, AA 392, AA 462, AA 519.2, AA 700, B 94, C 10.1, C 25.6, M 3, M 77, Y 120
Forbes
AA 2.38
Ford
AA 364, B 6, B 41, B 131, B 141, DE 30, DI 27, M 89, S 56
Forest Avenue
AA 232.3, Y 26
Forest Hill
AA 179
Forest Hill Cemetery
AA 244.25
Forest Lawn Cemetery
DE 65
Forest Street
AA 196.1, AA 196.3, AA 196.4, AA 196.5, Y 7
Fort Sumter
AA 666
Fosdich School
S 46
Foster Bridge
AA 516.8, AA 516.9, AA 516.10, AA 516.11, AA 516.18
Foster Mill
AA 268.1, AA 268.2, AA 268.3, AA 268.4, 268.5, AA 268.6, AA 268.7, AA 268.8, AA 268.S, AA 449, AA 516.5, AA 516.12, AA 516.13, AA, 516.14, AA 516.17, AA 516.19, AA 516.20
Foster Road
AA 516.15, AA 516.16
Foster's Station
AA 320, AA 681
Foundry
M 48
Fountain House
M 35, M 99
Fountain Street
AA 27B
Fourth Avenue
AA 23, AA 29G, AA 77, AA 123, AA 131, AA 221.8, AA 241.2, AA 244.2, AA 244.22
AA, 257.1, AA 257.2, AA 257.3, AA 257.4, AA 257.5, AA 313, AA 316, AA 328, AA 386
AA 421, AA, 454, AA 471, AA 472, AA 479, AA 494, AA, 503.5, AA 707, AA 710, AA 716, AA 720
Fourth Street
DE 87, DE 88
Fourth Ward
AA 28B
Frain Landing
Y 56
Frain's Lake School
DI 20, DI 26
Frank
AA 89
Fraternities
AA 254.5, AA 680
Freeman
C 1.26
Freeman Brothers
C 7.2
Freeman House
M 43
Freeman and Cummings Company
C 1.26
French
B 105
French Landing
Y 56
Fresh Aire Taxi
B 41
Frey
AA 385
Frieze Building
AA 221.31
Fritz Park
AA 59, AA 542
Fuller Road
AA 29J, AA 104, AA 273.64
Subject Index: G-I
G.A.R.
DE 65, Y 138
GL Thornton General Store
Y 24
GL Thornton Real Estate
Y 24
Gala Day
B 63, B 96
Gale
DI, 3
Gale School
DI 24
Galpin
DI 31, DI 34, DI 35
Gambel
B 63
Gas Company
AA 241.6
Gas Stations
AA 273.35, AA 537, Y 47
Gates
AA 315, DE 37
Geddes
AA 53
Geddes Avenue
AA 515, AA 515.6, AA 515.7, AA 515.8
Geddes Dam
AA 515.9
Geddes Pond
AA 515.5, AA 515.8
Geddes Power Plant
AA 515.2, AA 515.3, AA 515.4, AA, 515.10, AA 515.11, AA 515.12
Geddes Road
AA 29J, AA 104, AA 179, AA 221.20, AA, 230.15, AA 231.9, AA 259.1, AA 259.2, AA, 259.3, AA 292, AA 401
Geddes School
DI 15, DI 22
Geddesburg
AA 282.5
Geer
Y 131
German
AA 509
German Church
AA 567, CM 73, S 1
German Methodist Church
AA 707
German-American Day
AA 134, AA 360
Germania Hall
AA 437, AA 526, AA 526
Gilbert
M 120
Gilbert Park
Y 3
Gilmore and Fisk Books
AA 251.15
Gitre
B 62
Glazier
AA 244.11, C 1.1, C 1.8, C 1.9, C 1.14, C, 1.20, C, 1.27, C 2.1, C 2.6, C 2.14, C 2.16, C 2.18, C 6.2, C 9.2, C 9.4, C 13.7, C 15.5, C 22.7, CM 65
Glazier Building
AA 244.11
Glazier State Savings Bank
C 15.4
Glazier Stove Company
C 1.1, C 1.8, C 1.9, C 1.14, C, 1.17, C 1.20, C 2.1, C 2.6, C 2.14, C 2.16, C 2.18, C 6.2, C 7.2, C 9.2, C 9.4, C 15.5, C 22.7, CM 11, CM 65
Glen Avenue
AA 230.4
Glen Street
AA 29D
Glen's Service Garage
AA 510
Glick
CM 42
Glick's Department Store
CM 42
Goetz
AA 272.4, AA 384, AA 441
Goetz Cafe
AA 384
Goetz Meat Market
AA 272.4, AA 441
Goldman
AA 137
Goldman Brothers
AA 137
Golf
AA 701
Gooding
Y 115
Goodspeed
Y 104
Goodyear
AA 221.15
Goodyear Tires
AA 254.8
Goodyear and St. James Store
AA 221.15
Gordon Hall
DE 82
Gordon House
DE 70
Gorman Funeral Home
DE 78
Gospel Church
DE 91
Goucher
B 125
Government
AA 2.33, AA 11, AA 14, AA 29A, AA 29B, AA 29C, AA 29D, AA 29E, AA 29F, AA 29H, AA 291, AA 291, AA 29K, AA 29L, AA 29M, AA 290, AA 29P, AA 29Q, AA 29R, AA 29S
AA 31B, AA 36B, AA 54, AA 65, AA 66, AA 94, AA 116, AA 170, AA 217, AA 221.28, AA 225, AA 233.2, AA 238, AA 241.2, AA 244.18, AA 244.26, AA 244.29
AA 251.14, AA 284, AA 318, AA 418, AA 430, AA 453, AA 458, AA 473, AA 489', AA 493, AA 503.2, AA 666, AA 682, AA 720
B 27, B 32, B 116, C 5.1, C 5.2, C 11, C 13.8, CM 7, M 21, M 68, M 81, M 112, Y 122
Grace Bible Church
AA 465
Grand Army of the Republic
B 16, B 66, CM 79, DE 65, 1 138
Grand River
B 65
Grand River Avenue
B 4, B 11, B 14, B 26, B 36, B 4, B 44, B 72, B 76, B 87, B 93, B 95, B 98, 99, B 107, B 118, B 131, B 133
Grand River Street
B 57, B 73
Grant
C, 1.31, C 8.1
Grant & Wood Manufacturing Company
C 1.31, C 8.1
Gray
DE, 90, DE 90, S 40
Green
M, 13, Y 57
Green Hotel
M 13, M 51, M 52
Greenhouse
AA 21
Gregory
AA 260, AA 277.1, AA 277.2, AA 278.1, AA, 278.2, AA 278.3
Gregory Aircraft Corporation
AA 260
Gregory House
AA 244.18
Gregory House Hotel
AA 251.15
Greyhound, Bus Depot
AA 241.4
Grocery Stores
AA 617, AA 618, CM 8.1, CM 8.2, D 461, Y 99
Gross
S, 50, S 51
Gwinner
AA 27C, AA 27E
Gymnasiums
AA 185C, AA 273.3, Y 2
HMS Pinafore
AA 81, AA 82, Y 85
Haarer
AA 360, AA 507.3
Haeussler
M 35, M 42
Haeussler, & Kingsley Drug Store
M 42
Halderness
B 55
Hale and Smith Bank
AA 665
Hall
AA 2.24, AA 2.24, AA 228.11, AA 255.7, AA 517, AA 518, AA 571, AA 575, AA 573, AA 576, AA, 577, AA 578
Hall Road
CM 47
Hall's Greenhouse
AA 228.1, AA 228.10
Haller
AA 219, M 9, M 10
Haller's Jewelry
AA 219
Haller's Meat Market
M 9, M 10
Hamburg
B 146
Hamilton Block
AA 221.7, AA 221.8, AA 221.8, AA 313
Hammond
AA 26C
Hancock
Y 116
Hangsterfer
AA 151
Hangsterfer Block
AA 34C
Hangsterfer Building
AA 266.1, AA 288
Hanner
C 12
Hardware Stores
CM 78, DE 55, DE 101
Hardy
Y, 58
Harper
S 21
Harrar Building
AA 522
Harris
DE 13
Harris Hall
AA 121, AA 205, AA 679
Harrison Avenue
C 6.3
Harrison Street
C 1.11
Hartman
B 49, B 124
Hartman Saloon
B 49, B 124
Hartmena
B 49
Hasselbach
DI 30
Hauessler
M 99, M 102, M 103
Hauessler & Kingsley Drug Store
M 103
Haven Hall
AA 273.14, AA 273.34
Haven Street
AA 5
Hawkins House
Y 129, Y 143
Hayner Real Estate
B 49
Heinzman
AA 91, AA 90
Heinzman and Son
AA 91, AA 90
Heller
AA 264B
Helms
CM 83
Henry
Y 82
Herbst
AA 472
Heron
AA 2.41
Herrick
AA 244.22
Herrick and Bohnet
AA 244.22
Hertler
AA 419, AA 420, AA 519.3
Hertler Brothers
AA 419, AA 519.3
Hewitt Road
Y 59
Higgins
M 119
High Schools, see also Schools
AA 514, AA 519.2, AA 676, B 56, B 61, B 89, B 94, B 111, B 117, B 135, B 138
C 1.11, C 1.29, C 10.1, C 15.3, CM 81, DE 69, M 6, M 15, M 90, M 117, Y 106, Y 119, Y 120
High Street
Y 142
Highways
AA 232.2
Hill Auditorium
AA 88, AA 265, AA 273.8
Hill Street
AA 5, AA 49, AA 185, AA 572, AA 574, AA, 627, AA 712
Hines
B 41
Hiram Pierce House
C 27
Hoad
AA 648
Hoelzle
AA 529
Hoey
DE 62, DE 63
Hoff
AA 255.10, AA 255.10
Holen
AA 244.19
Holidays
AA 14, AA 19, AA 20, AA 132, AA 134, AA 162, AA 360, AA 502.1, AA 502.2, AA 519.3, B 96
B, 116, C 1.15, C 1.16, C 1.17, C 3.9, CM 16, DI 5, M 44, M 124, S 55, Y 78, Y 84
Hollier Automobile Plant
C 13.1
Hollier Automobiles
C 13.2
Holmes
AA 140, C 22.5
Holmes Mercantile Company
C 7.2, C 22.'5
Holmes' University Livery
AA 140
Homecoming
B 35, B 38, B 39, B 135
Homer Ives Home
C 4.3
Honey
DE 34, DE 36, DE 36, DE 61
Honey Drug Store
DE 34, DE 61
Hoover
AA 273.54
Hoover Place
AA 273.27, AA 273.54
Hoover Steel Ball Company
CM 53
Hope Street
B 133
Horses
AA 26B, AA 26C, AA 68, AA 110, AA 147, AA 159, AA 195, AA 204, AA 206, AA 229A, AA 229B, AA 229C, AA, 234, AA 258.1, AA 258.21 AA 258.6, AA 289, AA, 328, AA 403
B 31 B 151 B 21, B 59, B 72, B, 75, B 126, B 129, C 2.17, C 15.2, C 25.4, D, 99, DE 9, DE 21, DE 42, DE 48, DE 74, DI 32, M 51, Y 23
Horses and Carriages
AA 135, AA 195, AA 204, AA 206, AA 234, AA 289, B 3, B 43, B 59, B 63, B 78, B 102, B 107, C 2.17, CM 9, D 99, DE 21, DE, 42, DE 48, DE 74, DI 32, M 116, Y 23, Y 91
Hospitals
AA 29J, AA 196.3, AA 196.4, AA 231.5, AA, 231.10, AA 244.23, AA 246, AA 273.7, AA, 273.20, AA 273.46, AA 273.48, AA 273.62, AA, 273.63, AA 273.64, AA 338, AA 339, AA 368, AA, 427, AA 473, B 29, Y 126
Hot-Air Balloon
M 31
Hotel Simpson
M 547
Hotel Whitney
AA 29P
Hotels
AA 27, AA 103, AA 103A, AA 103B, AA 103C, AA, 221.34, AA 244.16, AA 251.15, AA 266.3, AA, 275, AA 284, AA 454, AA 581
B 26, B 47, B, 73, B 82, B 87, B 118, C 2.8, C 21.1, CM 76, DE 51, DE 76, M 547, M 13, M 19, M 52, Y 24, Y 52
Howard
AA 606
Howlett
C 3.8
Howlett Home
C 3.8
Hoyt School
S 56
Hubbard
AA 2.31
Huber
M 89
Hudson-Essex
AA 469
Hunt Hardware Store
AA 67
Hunt
AA 660
Hunter
AA 469
Hunter's Garage
AA 469
Hunting
AA 470
Huron Block
AA 51, AA 533
Huron Mills
Y 124
Huron River
AA 53, AA 104, AA 155, AA 169, AA 178, AA 197, AA 221.21, AA 221.26, AA 221.27, AA 230.15, AA 232.7, AA 236.2, AA 236.3, AA 244.23, AA 256.1, AA 256.2, AA 256.3, AA 259.1, AA 259.2, AA 259.3
AA 268.1, AA 268.2, AA 268.3, AA 268.4, AA 268.5, AA 268.6, AA 268.7, AA 268.8, AA 268.9, AA 269.1, AA 269.2, AA 269.3, AA 269.4, AA 269.5, AA 269.6, AA 269.7, AA 269.8, AA 269.9, AA 269.10, AA 269.11
AA 272.1, AA 274.1, AA 337, AA 411, AA 484, AA 492, AA 501, AA 516.15, AA 681, B 143, DE 17, Y 19, Y 46
Huron River Bridge
AA 259.1, AA 259.2, AA259.3
Huron River Drive
AA 281.2, AA 516.15, AA715
Huron River Manufacturing Company
AA 508
Huron Road
Y 124
Huron Street
AA 7, AA 8, AA 9, AA 14, AA 39, AA 40, AA 41, AA 42, AA 54, AA 61, AA 71, AA 79, AA 80, AA 98, AA 99, AA
100, AA 101, AA 109, AA 121, AA 122, AA 132, AA 139, AA 163, AA 164, AA 186, AA 191
AA 205, AA 214, AA 219, AA 221.4, AA 221.7, AA 221.8, AA 221.25, AA 230.2, AA 241.2, AA 241.4, AA 241.5, AA 244.4, AA 244.10, AA 244.18, AA 244.20, AA 244.21, AA 244.29
AA 251.3, AA 251.7, AA 251.8, AA 251.12, AA 251.16, AA 251.25, AA 252.2, AA 253, AA 254.6, AA 258.4, AA 258.5
AA 270.3, AA 282.1, AA 308, AA 313, AA 319, AA 336, AA 358, AA 361, AA 367, AA 370, AA 377, AA 378, AA 381, AA 386
AA 422, AA 424, AA 426, AA 436, AA 451, AA 454, AA 497, AA 523, AA 530, AA 532, AA 569, AA 621, AA 679, AA 708
DE 79, DE 85, DE 104, Y1, Y 22, Y 36, Y 99, Y ill, Y 145, Y 146, Y 147, Y 148
Huron Valley Building
AA 471, AA 472
Huron-Jackson Road
AA 534
Hutchins
AA 273.50, AA 273.50
Hutzel
AA 135, AA 303
Hutzel and Company
AA 131, AA 133, AA 134, AA 135
Hutzel's Hustlers
AA 303
Ice Skating
AA 155, M 59
Icehouse
AA 274.1
Independence Day
AA 14, DI 5, M 44, M 124, S 55
Indianapolis
AA 475
Industry
AA 138, AA 185B, AA 239B, AA 244.27, AA 4, B 71, B 84, DE 9, DE 57, Y 80
Ingalls Street
AA 190, AA 533
Interiors
AA 2.40, AA 32B, AA 35B, AA 55, AA 79, AA 80, AA 90, AA 101, AA 103A, AA 103B, AA 103C, AA 139, AA 254.1, AA 254.2
AA 266.2, AA 266.3, AA 273.21, AA 273.29, AA 273.59, AA 285, AA 311, AA 313, AA 324, AA 327, AA 329, AA 331, AA 335, AA 346, AA 348, AA 349, AA 382, AA 383
AA 409, AA 416, AA 421, AA 434, AA 463, AA 472, AA 571, AA 648, AA 649, AA 655, AA 656, AA 657, AA 691, AA 692, AA 693
B 54, B 124, C 2.16, C 11, C 19, CM 23, CM 48, CM 73, CM 75, CM 10.5, CM 39, CM 44, CM 44
DE 8, DE 49, DE 101, DE 114, M 9, M 43, M 65, M 78, M 99, M 106, M 118, S 51, Y 2, Y 53, Y 114, Y 115, Y 130, Y 141, Y 143
Interurbans, see also Streetcars
AA 7, AA 8, AA 9, 49, AA 93, AA 98, AA 99, AA 100, AA 101, 160, AA 162, AA 163, AA 164, AA 165, AA 1, AA 244.14
AA 272.6, AA 352, AA 354, AA 35, AA 371, AA 377, AA 378, AA 379, AA 446, 523
CM 30, CM 30, S 6, S 12, S 19, Y 33, 50, Y 60, Y 63, Y 66, Y 70, Y 89, Y 98
Iron Bridge
M 75
Island Lake
B 98, B 126, B 134, B 142, B 144
Island Lake Camp
Y 93
Island Park
AA 22D, AA 582, AA 624, AA 625, DI 18
Island Park Bridge
AA 582
Ives
C 4.3
Subject Index: J-L
J.H. Lambert's University Shoe Shop
AA 433, AA 434
Jackson
AA 359, CM 11
Jackson Limited
AA 359
Jackson Railroad
S 31, Y 34, Y 39, Y 67, Y 68, Y, Y 70
Jackson Road
AA 240
Jackson Street
M 19
Jacobson's
AA 432
James Tom's Greenhouse
AA 21
Jefferson School
AA 402
Jefferson Street
AA 45, AA 254.7, AA 254.8, AA 254., AA 707
Jenness
Y 26
Jenney
AA 173, AA 273.53
Jenter
M 95
Johnson
AA 648, DE 13
Jolly Bar
AA 557
Jones
B 30
Judson
DI 40
KLG Band
DE 10, DE 75
Kalb
C 25.3, C 25.8
Kalb's Restaurant
C 25.3f C 25.8f
Kalmbach
C 3.14
Keehn
B 90
Kellogg
C 29f
Kelsey Museum
AA 390f
Kempf
C 13.5, C 13.6
Kempf Bank
C 3.14, C 13.6
Kerrytown
AA 17, AA 18
Kieff
M 66, M 66
Kieff House
M 34, M 34
Kimball
CM 82
Kimble
M 56, M 80
Kimble & Schmidt Stone Boat Factory
M 56f M 80
King
B 79
Kingsley
M 42, M 79, M 103
Kingsley Street
AA 493, AA 494
Kirchhofer
M 117f
Kitchen
AA 273.21
Klaudt
AA 6
Kline
M 1
Kline's
AA 565
Klingler
CM 12.3
Klingler Meats
CM 12.3
Knapp
M 11, M 11
Knight
AA 232.3f
Knorpp
M 87f M 88f M 89f M 95f
Koebbe
M 97
Koebbe Threshing Machine
M 97
Koppler
AA 606
Kurtz
AA 232.8
Kyer-Whitker Wholesale Grocers
AA 531
LT Freeman and Company
C 1.4
Labor Day
AA 134, AA 519.3. AA 519.3
Laboratories
AA 2.18, AA 296, AA 408, AA 431, AA 46
Ladies Aid
DI 39
Ladies Library
Y 127
Ladies Library Association
AA 282.1
Lake Shore
M 26, M 47, M 67f
Lake Shore Railroad
M 67
Lake Shore Station
Y 107
Lakeland
B 146f
Lakes
AA 272.6, AA 516.1, B 42, B 98, B 115, B 126, B 134f B 142, B 144f Y 102
Lamb
Y 115f
Lambert
AA 432, AA 433, AA 434
Law School
AA 2.9, AA 2.9, AA 58, AA 58, AA 73, AA, 73, AA 251.27, AA 251.28, AA 251.29, AA, 273.14, AA 273.14, AA 273.65A, AA 273.65A, AA, 273.65A, AA 273.65B, AA 273.65B, AA 273.65B, AA 405, AA 405, AA 463
Lehman
M 95
Leith and Case Agency
B 110
Leitz
B 141, B 142, B 143
Leland San
Y 126
Leland's
B 74, B 113
Leslie
DI 3
Letta Jones
B 30
Leutheuser
S 29
Levan
B 41
Lewis
AA 67, C 13.3, Y 131
Lewis Spring and Axle Company
C 13.1, C 13.2, C 13.3
Lewis-Geer Manufacturing Company
Y 131
Liberty Bond
AA 227
Liberty Day
Y 84
Liberty Market
AA 442
Liberty Street
AA 26B, AA 26D, AA 34B, AA 34D, AA 126, AA 128, AA 133, AA 136, AA 208, AA 209, AA 210, AA 215, AA 216, AA 221.3, AA 221.11, AA 221.15, AA 221.36, AA 230.5, AA 230.8, AA 230.12, AA 232.8, AA 241.7
AA 257.1, AA 257.2, AA 257.3, AA 257.4, AA 257.5, AA 273.30, AA 316, AA 360, AA 432, AA 441, AA 444, AA 445, AA 476, AA 499, AA 507.1, AA 507.2, AA 522, AA 527, AA 566
AA 643, AA 644, AA 645, AA 646, AA 647, AA 648, AA 649, AA 650, AA 651, AA 652, AA 653, AA 654, AA 655, AA 656, AA 657
Libraries, see also University Library
AA 2.13, AA, 2.14, AA 2.19, AA 2.21, AA 223, AA 273.11C, AA 273.49, AA 282.1, AA 295, AA 391, AA 431, AA 431, AA 463, B 27, C 2.8, C 26, DE 1, DE, 2, DE 12, M 112, S 2, Y 127
Lincoln Street
C 1.4
Lindenschmitt-Apfel & Company
AA 254.1, AA 254.2, AA, 254.3
Litchfield
DE 33
Livesay
AA 290
Livingston County
B 75
Logging
DE 9, DE 57
Longshore
AA 230.9
Longshore Drive
AA 29K, AA 626, AA 628, AA 629
Lorrin Mills
AA 497
Lost in New York
AA 291
Love
AA 244.14
Lowell Street
Y 95
Luick
AA 17, AA 18, AA 60
Luick Lumber Company
AA 17, AA 18, AA 19, AA 60
Lurie Terrace
AA 497
Luther League
B 104
Lutheran
B 69, B 70
Lutheran Church
AA 709
Lynch
M 112
Lyons
AA 2.32, AA 2.32, B 143
Subject Index: M-O
Maccabee
Y 78
Machine Specialty Company
AA 273.38
Mack
AA 92, AA 221.22, AA 221.23, AA221.24
Mack and Company
AA 15, AA 92, AA 221.22, AA 221.23, AA 221.24
Mack's Garage
AA 567
Macon Road
S 13, S 56
Madison Street
AA 175, AA 698, C 2.4, M 34
Mahlke
AA 541
Main Four Corners
B 118, B 122
Main Street -- Ann Arbor
AA 8, AA 9, AA 10, AA 11, AA 14, AA 15, AA 31A, AA 34A, AA 34B, AA 34D, AA 34E, AA 35A, AA 35B, AA 35C, AA 54, AA 64, AA 67, AA 69, AA 85, AA 86, AA 98, AA 99
AA 100, AA 101, AA 109, AA 116, AA 118, AA 120, AA 122, AA 128, AA 129, AA 134, AA 135, AA 160, AA 163, AA 180, AA 186
AA 214, AA 215, AA 216, AA 218, AA 220, AA 221.3, AA 221.13, AA 221.15, AA 221.23, AA 221.24, AA 221.36, AA 224, AA 225, AA 230.11, AA 230.12, AA 232.7, AA 232.9, AA 233.2
AA 241.1, AA 241.4, AA 241.5, AA 244.4, AA 244.5, AA 244.8, AA 244.11, AA 244.18, AA 244.20, AA 244.21, AA 244.29, AA 251.15, AA 254.1, AA 254.2, AA 254.3, AA 256.3, AA 266.1, AA 266.2, AA 273.38, AA 281.2, AA 288, AA 291
AA 307, AA 308, AA 311, AA 312, AA 314, AA 316, AA 319, AA 326, AA 327, AA 336, AA 342, AA 360, AA 367, AA 370, AA 381
AA 444, AA 448, AA 451, AA 458, AA 477, AA 486, AA 495, AA 503.2, AA 521, AA 527, AA 531, AA 537, AA 562, AA 563, AA 565, AA 564, AA 566, AA 569, AA 587
AA 611, AA 662, AA 664, AA 671, AA 682, AA 686, AA 687, AA 717, AA 719
Main Street -- Btightonst
B 24, B 33, B 38, B 43, B 60, B 76, B 77, B 78, B 81, B 88, B 98, B 99, B 102, B 118, B 140
Main Street -- Chelsea
C 1.1, C 1.2, C 1.3, C 1.10, C 1.18, C 1.23, C 1.24, C 1.27, C 1.33, C 1.34, C 2.2, C 2.11, C 2.12, C 2.14, C 3.3, C 3.9, C 3.10, C 3.13, C 3.17, C 7.1, C 9.3, C 15.1, C 15.4, C 15.6, C 17.1, C 17.2, C 17.4, C 20, C 21.1, C 22.1, C 22.2, C 22.3, C 22.4, C 22.5, C 22.7, C 25.3, C 25.8, C 25.13
Main Street -- Chelsea-Manchester
CM 16, CM 43, CM 5.1, CM 5.2, CM 5.3, CM 5.4
DE 18, DE 20, DE 21, DE 23, DE 34, DE 37, DE 41, DE 48, DE 52, DE 59, DE 60, DE 61, DE 73, DE 74, DE 76, DE 103, M 9, M 10, M 12, M 13, M 28, M 36, M 51, M 88, M 96, M 98, S 7, S 8, S 6, S 12, S 15
Main Street -- Dexter
DE 18, DE 20, DE 21, DE 23, DE 34, DE 37, DE 41, DE 48, DE 52, DE 59, DE 60, DE 61, DE 73, DE 74, DE 76, DE 103
Majestic Theater
AA 241.7, AA 323, AA 500
Main Street -- Manchester
M 9, M 10, M 12, M 13, M 28, M 36, M 51, M 88, M 96, M 98
S 7, S 8, S 6, S 12, S 15
Main Street -- Saline
S 7, S 8, S 6, S 12, S 15
Malloy's Harness Shop
AA 421
Maltby Lake
B 115
Maltby Road
B 45
Man
AA 2.39
Manchester Dandies Club
M 53
Manchester Enterprise
M 85, M 86
Manchester Handle Company
M 60
Manchester High School
M 6, M 90
Manchester Orchestra
M 64
Manchester Water Tower
M 50
Mape
CM 77
Maple Road
AA 320
Maple Road Bridge
AA 320
Maps
AA 28A, AA 28B, AA 28C, AA 28D, AA 30, C 2.19, CM 55, Y 51
Markham
AA 306
Markham Pottery
AA 306
Marriage
AA 597, CM 64
Martin-Haller Furniture
AA 257.1, AA 257.2. AA 257.3, AA 257.4, AA 257.5
Mason Hall
252.3, AA 251.2
Masonic Block
AA 122, B 66
Masonic Lodge
DI 9
Masonic Temple
Y 73
Masons Lodge
DI 9
Maynard Street
AA 13, AA 241.7, AA 273.30, AA 499, AA, 609
Mayor's Day
M 95
McCarten
AA 423
McCarten Brothers
AA 423
McCarten Brothers Market
AA 423
McCullough
AA 290
McDermott
Y 49
McKay Street